goshopping.com 2012-10-29

# Goshopping.com - privacy policy

## 1\. INTRODUCTION AND GENERAL TERMS

Your privacy is very important to GoShopping.com. Therefore, GoShopping.com is committed to protecting your personal information when you are using GoShopping.com services. This privacy policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide while using the GoShopping.com website. In order to provide you with GoShopping.com services, we are sometimes required to collect information about you. This privacy policy explains what GoShopping.com does to keep information about you private and secure.

## 2\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

GoShopping.com might collect personally identifying information when you register for a GoShopping.com account, when you use certain GoShopping.com services, including the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the website. We also collect certain information that your web browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser language and type, access times and referring website addresses.  
GoShopping.com uses "cookies" to recognize returning users automatically. Cookies used by the website might contain your user name and e-mail address. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to store and read information, and allows us to display your website preferences and search criteria whenever you visit GoShopping.com.  
We might gather information about your geographical location by determining where your computer is located. We do this to provide either localized service or faster service by sending localized content to your server.  
We might require other information for tracking or verifying compliance with our policies, abiding by federal, state, and local laws and for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes.  
From time to time, we might use your information for unanticipated uses, such as notification of new services, announcements, and general communications.  
If our information practices materially change, we will post such changes to the website before we use your data for these new purposes.  
If you are concerned about how we use your information, please periodically check this privacy policy.  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children, and we will destroy such information if it anyone discloses it to us without proper parental consent.

## 3\. USE OF INFORMATION

GoShopping.com uses the personal information you provide to deliver services, respond to your inquiries, or to process your requests. We might share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services that we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third parties for their marketing use.

## 4\. PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your Internet connection to our servers. We have implemented technology and security policies, rules, and other measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also protect your information by requiring that all our employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. Only authorized personnel handle your data, and our database servers have a backup system to prevent loss of data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure, and we will not be held liable should a third party illegally obtain your personal information. While we have made a great effort to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You do so at your own risk.

## 5\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

GoShopping.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. GoShopping.com might send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people if we have your consent to share the information or we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested.  
We might transfer information about you if GoShopping.com acquires, or is acquired by or merged with, another company. In this event, GoShopping.com will notify you before transferring your information and before it becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
We might share your personal information with our affiliates, consultants, vendors, and service providers who assist us in maintaining the website and providing related services, such as online registration for events.

## 6\. ACCESS OF INFORMATION

If you believe that any information collected by our website is in error, you may edit your personal profile at any time. You can directly edit your user profile on our GoShopping.com website. If we terminate or suspend your account, we might maintain some data to prevent re-registration.

## 7\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The GoShopping.com website contains links to other websites. GoShopping.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. If you have concerns about how another website collects and uses information about you, read that website’s privacy policy.

## 8\. CHOICE/OPT-OUT POLICY

GoShopping.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving e-mails from us or from our partners and advertisers at the point where we request information about you, the visitor. You can choose to opt-out of receiving any e-mail communications from us and from our sharing your contact data with our partners and with advertisers for direct marketing purposes.

## 9\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

GoShopping.com might occasionally revise this privacy policy. We will notify you by e-mail or through a prominent notice on our website. We encourage you to review this privacy policy periodically to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of our services constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates.
